McWhirter, Mrs. F.T. mss., 1873-1974 LMC 2183
Lilly Library
McWhirter, Mrs. F.T. mss.
1873-1974
Lilly Library
McWhirter, F. T., Mrs. (Felix Tony), 1859-1952.
LMC 2183
7 Boxes
2 folios 2 oversize folios
The McWhirter, Mrs. F.T. mss., 1840-1979, are papers of Luella Frances (Smith) McWhirter (Mrs. Felix Tony McWhirter), 1859-1952, clubwoman.
Access Restrictions
This collection is open for research.
Many collections are housed offsite; retrieval requires advance notice. Please make an appointment a minimum of one week in advance of your visit.
Acquisition Information
Gift: 1953-1974
Arrangement
The collection is organized into the following series: I. Subjects; II. Scrapbooks; III. Printed; IV. Photographs; V. Miscellaneous.
Biographical Note
Career:
October 1, 1859 Born at Perrysville, Vermillion County, Indiana
Undated Daughter of the Reverend Hezekiah Smith and Susan Davis (Marsters) Smith
Undated Educated at East Tennessee Wesleyan College, Athens, Tennessee, and DePauw University
November 18, 1878 Married Felix Tony McWhirter
Undated Following marriage resided at Athens, Tennessee and Greencastle, Indiana, where Mr. McWhirter was member of the English Department of DePauw University
1888 Moved to Indianapolis
1893-1896 Indiana W.C.T.U. treasurer
1896-1900 Indiana W.C.T.U. president
1927-1937 and 1940 Indiana W.C.T.U. trustee
1940-1952 Indiana W.C.T.U. honorary president
1897-1913 and 1919-1945 Editor, The Message, official paper of the Indiana W.C.T.U.
1900-1936 Director, Peoples' State Bank of Indianapolis
1907-1909 President, Woman's Research Club
1908 Appointed to represent Indiana in Congress of Mothers, Washington, D.C.
1911 President, seventh [Indiana] Federation of Clubs
1911-1913 Indiana Federation of Clubs, president
1938-1952 Indiana Federation of Clubs, honorary president
1924-1927 Indiana Federation of Clubs, chairman, American Home Department
1916-1918 Indiana Federation of Clubs, organizer, War Victory Commission
1911 One of organizers, Woman's Franchise League of Indiana, vice-president
1912 Founder, Woman's Department Club of Indianapolis
1922-1926 President, Woman's Department Club of Indianapolis
1912 General Federation of Women's Clubs, president, State Presidents' Club
1916-1920 General Federation of Women's Clubs, director for Indiana
1916-1924 General Federation of Women's Clubs, transportation chairman
1925-1927 General Federation of Women's Clubs, chairman, War Victory Commission, chairman, Extension Department
1932-1938 General Federation of Women's Clubs, trustee
Undated General Federation of Women's Clubs, chairman, Federation Foundation Fund for six Midwest states
1917 President, Legislative Council of Indiana Women
1917 Vice-president, Indiana Dry Federation
1917-1945 Trustee, Robert W. Long College for Women (to be established)
1918-1920 Director, United States Good Roads
1922 Chairman, Indianapolis drive for building funds, Women's Union Christian Colleges in the Orient
1926-1937 president, Indiana Conference Deaconess Board, Methodist Episcopal Church
1931-1932 Member, President's Conference on Home Building and Home Ownership
1932 Chairman, Woman's Loyalty Committee for Indiana, United Protestant Church Loyalty Crusade
1932-1934 Indiana White Cross Guild, Methodist Hospital, Indianapolis, president
1934-1952 Indiana White Cross Guild, Methodist Hospital, Indianapolis, president emeritus
1936 Member, Jury of award on Model Homes of Indiana, Federal Housing Administration
1936-1938 National League of American Pen Women, charter member and vice-president for Indiana branch
1942 Regional mother, Golden Rule Foundation
December 10, 1952 Died
Trustee: Taylor University
Historian: May Wright Sewall State Council of Women
Member:
Caroline Scott Harrison Chapter of the Daughters of the American Revolution
Society of Indiana Pioneers
Epsilon Sigma Omicron
Central Avenue Methodist Episcopal Church, Indianapolis, Indiana
Association of Parliamentarians
Woman's Press Club of Indiana
Biographical accounts of Mrs. McWhirter appear also in Blanche Foster Boruff's Women of Indiana... (Indianapolis, [c1941]), p. 199 and Mildred Marshall Scouller's Women Who Man Our Clubs... (Philadelphia, 1934), pp. 146-148.
Scope and Content Note
The Subjects series contains correspondence, addresses, constitutions and by-laws, minutes of meetings, membership lists, histories of organizations, yearbooks, programs, and publicity materials.
Correspondents in the Subjects series include: Mildred (Carlson) Ahlgren, Albion (Fellows) Bacon, Bertha (Crosley) Ball, Arcada Campbell (Stark) Balz, Eliza A. (Cooper) Blaker, Ella Alexander Boole, Evangeline Cory Booth, Marie Caroline Brehm, William Lowe Bryan, Mary (Quick) Burnet, Amos William Butler, Nannie C. (Lucas) Canine, Eleanore Elliott Carroll, Grace (Julian) Clarke, Mamie (White) Colvin, Clara Ruth (Meid) Compton, Milton Conover, Sallie (Southall) Cotten, Lucy (Jennings) Dickinson, Nettie A. (Geiger) Downey, Saidie (Orr) Dunbar, Carrie Belle (Tyler) Fenton, Irving Fisher, Gerald Rudolph Ford, James Ford, William Fortune, James Putnam Goodrich, Anna Adams Gordon, John Matthew Gries, Lottie (Lyons) Grow, James Franklin Hanly, Rolla Neil Harger, Ida (Husted) Harper, Mary Garrett Hay, William Harrison Hays, Catharine (Spicer) Hitch, Herbert Hoover, Mary Hannah (Hanchett) Hunt, John Newell Hurty, Allan Jackson, Charles Bacon Jackson, Mrs. Haute (Tarkington) Jameson, Evelyn (Hageman) Jaqua, Rose Carolyn (Byers) Katterhenry, Helen Adams Keller, John Harvy Kellogg, Edward Joseph Kelly, Araminta (Cooper) Kern, Estella M. (Stiles) King, Helen (McCreadie) Knight, Robert Patterson Lamont, Roberta (Campbell) Lawson, Mary Ashton (Rice) Livermore, Katherine (Huber) Ludlow, Louis Leon Ludlow, Warren Terry McCray, Felix Tony McWhirter, Nancy Caroline (Tyree) McWhirter, Shailer Mathews, Mable (Warner) Millikan, James Atwell Mount, Harry Stewart New, Vida Newsom, R. Earl Peters, Grace (Smith) Pettijohn, Amelia Waring Platter, Anne (Carlisle) Porter, Bertha (Kelsey) Poston, Samuel Moffett Ralson, Anna Steese (Sausser) Richardson, Maude Ellen (Lucas) Rumpler, Elizabeth (Gunn) Seebirt, May (Wright) Sewall, Albert Shaw, Margaret (Espy) Vennedge Sheridan, Mary Belle (King) Sherman, Bettie M. Sipple, Hezekiah Smith, Mabel (Johnson) Smith, Rodney Smith, Susan Davis (Marsters) Smith, Elizabeth (Tipton) Stanley, Sara (Messing) Stern, Lillian M. N. (Ames) Stevens, Katharine Adelia (Lente) Stevenson, James Arthur Stuart, Milo H. Stuart, Thomas Taggart, Booth Tarkington, Susan (Davis) Taylor, Elizabeth Ione (McDonald) Thornburgh, M. Clifford Townsend, Phebe (Kerrick) Warner, James Eli Watson, William Allen White, Cora (Young) Wiles, Frances Elizabeth Willard, Vella Alberta Winner, Alice (Ames) Winter, Evans Woollen, William Watson Woollen, John Granville Wooley, and Rose Emmet Young. Consult the Manuscripts Index in the Library for dates and locations of letters of individual correspondents.
Note on Indexing Term - "Medicine": Of interest are Committee minutes and newspaper clippings of the Jacob E. Wile Memorial Nurses' Home of the Indianapolis Methodist Hospital, papers of the White Cross Guild of the Indianapolis Methodist Hospital and one folder of 1925-1939 material related to the Missionary Medical College for Women, Vellore, India.
Note on Indexing Term - "Religion": Represented in the collection is material pertaining to the Indiana School of Religion, the Woman's Christian Temperance Union and the Methodist Episcopal Church and its various divisions such as the Women's Foreign Missionary Society and Women's Home Missionary Society.
Note on Indexing Term - "Women": Contains correspondence, diaries from 1894 to 1941, scrapbooks, and files of The Message, the official paper of the Indiana Women's Christian Temperance Union. Her papers document efforts of Indiana women to secure temperance reform and the ballot.
Temperance --Societies, etc.; Women --Societies and clubs.; Women --Suffrage --Indiana.; Medicine; Religion; Women; McWhirter, F. T., Mrs. (Felix Tony), 1859-1952. --Correspondence.; Daughters of the American Revolution. Caroline Scott Harrison Chapter (Indianapolis, Ind.); General Federation of Women's Clubs.; Golden Rule Foundation.; Indiana Federation of Clubs.; Woman's Christian Temperance Union.; Woman's Department Club (Indianapolis, Ind.)
- I. Subjects
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically after biographical and genealogical information, and letters of condolence on the death of Mrs. McWhirter.
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondents include:
  Albion (Fellows) Bacon
  Bertha (Crosley) Ball
  Arcada Campbell (Stark) Balz
  Eliza A. (Cooper) Blaker
  Ella Alexander Boole
  Evangeline Cory Booth
  Marie Caroline Brehm
  William Lowe Bryan
  Mary (Quick) Burnet
  Amos William Butler
  Nannie C. (Lucas) Canine
  Eleanore Elliott Carroll
  Grace (Julian) Clarke
  Mamie (White) Colvin
  Clara Ruth (Meid) Compton
  Milton Conover
  Sallie (Southall) Cotten
  Lucy (Jennings) Dickinson
  Nettie A. (Geiger) Downey
  Saidie (Orr) Dunbar
  Carrie Belle (Tyler) Fenton
  Irving Fisher
  Gerald Rudolph Ford
  James Ford
  William Fortune
  James Putnam Goodrich
  Anna Adams Gordon
  John Matthew Gries
  Lottie (Lyons) Grow
  James Franklin Hanly
  Rolla Neil Harger
  Ida (Husted) Harper
  Mary Garrett Hay
  William Harrison Hays
  Catharine (Spicer) Hitch
  Herbert Hoover
  Mary Hannah (Hanchett) Hunt
  John Newell Hurty
  Allan Jackson
  Charles Bacon Jackson
  Mrs. Haute (Tarkington) Jameson
  Evelyn (Hageman) Jaqua
  Rose Carolyn (Byers) Katterhenry
  Helen Adams Keller
  John Harvy Kellogg
  Edward Joseph Kelly
  Araminta (Cooper) Kern
  Estella M. (Stiles) King
  Helen (McCreadie) Knight
  Robert Patterson Lamont
  Roberta (Campbell) Lawson
  Mary Ashton (Rice) Livermore
  Katherine (Huber) Ludlow
  Louis Leon Ludlow
  Warren Terry McCray
  Felix Tony McWhirter
  Nancy Caroline (Tyree) McWhirter
  Shailer Mathews
  Mable (Warner) Millikan
  James Atwell Mount
  Harry Stewart New
  Vida Newsom
  R. Earl Peters
  Grace (Smith) Pettijohn
  Amelia Waring Platter
  Anne (Carlisle) Porter
  Bertha (Kelsey) Poston
  Samuel Moffett Ralson
  Anna Steese (Sausser) Richardson
  Maude Ellen (Lucas) Rumpler
  Elizabeth (Gunn) Seebirt
  May (Wright) Sewall
  Albert Shaw
  Margaret (Espy) Vennedge Sheridan
  Mary Belle (King) Sherman
  Bettie M. Sipple
  Hezekiah Smith
  Mabel (Johnson) Smith
  Rodney Smith
  Susan Davis (Marsters) Smith
  Elizabeth (Tipton) Stanley
  Sara (Messing) Stern
  Lillian M. N. (Ames) Stevens
  Katharine Adelia (Lente) Stevenson
  James Arthur Stuart
  Milo H. Stuart
  Thomas Taggart
  Booth Tarkington
  Susan (Davis) Taylor
  Elizabeth Ione (McDonald) Thornburgh
  M. Clifford Townsend
  Phebe (Kerrick) Warner
  James Eli Watson
  William Allen White
  Cora (Young) Wiles
  Frances Elizabeth Willard
  Vella Alberta Winner
  Alice (Ames) Winter
  Evans Woollen
  William Watson Woollen
  John Granville Wooley
  Rose Emmet Young
  - Biographical and genealogical, 1898-1970; (4 folders) (Box 1)
  - Letters of condolence on the death of Mrs. McWhirter, (3 folders) (Box 1)
  - Autographs (Box 1)
  - Badges (Box 1)
  - Better Homes in America:, 1924-1942; (5 folders) (Box 1)
  - Better Homes in America: publicity notebook, 1933 (Box 1)
  - Better Homes in America: newspaper clippings, 1934-1942 (Box 1)
  - Citizens Committee of One Thousand (Box 1)
  - Contests (Box 1)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution, (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Epsilon Sigma Omicron (Box 1)
  - Federation of Women's Boards of Foreign Missions of North America (Box 1)
  - Ford, Gerald Rudolph (Box 1)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs:, 1912-1929 (Box 1)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs:, 1930-1946 (Box 1)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs: Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs: Federation Foundation fund (Box 1)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs: State President's Club, 1912 (Box 1)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs: Committee on Federation Extension (Box 1)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs: Transportation Chairman, 1899-1924; (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs: World War Service Board (Box 2)
  - Golden Rule Foundation (Box 2)
  - Golden Rule Foundation. American Mother's Committee (Box 2)
  - Hoosier Salon Patron's Association. Hoosier Program Bureau (Box 2)
  - Indiana Association of Parliamentarians (Box 2)
  - Indiana Audubon Society (Box 2)
  - Indiana Dry Federation (Box 2)
  - Indiana Federation of Clubs:, 1909-1956; (6 folders) (Box 2)
  - Indiana Federation of Clubs: Newspaper clippings (Box 2)
  - Indiana Federation of Clubs: Department of the American Home, 1923-1941; (3 folders) (Box 2)
  - Indiana Federation of Clubs: Department of the American Home, newspaper clippings (Box 2)
  - Indiana Federation of Clubs: War Victory Commission, 1916-1918 (Box 2)
  - Indiana School of Religion (Box 2)
  - Indianapolis, IN, Methodist Hospital (Box 2)
  - Jacob E. Wile Memorial Nurses Home (Box 2)
  - White Cross Guild (Box 2)
  - White Cross Guild, newspaper clippings (Box 2)
  - Indianapolis Local Council of Women (Box 2)
  - International Council of Women (Box 2)
  - Invitations (Box 2)
  - Legislative Council of Indiana Women (Box 2)
  - McWhirter, Felix Tony: Condolences on death of (Box 2)
  - McWhirter, Felix Tony: To McWhirter, Mrs. Luella Frances (Smith) (Box 2)
  - McWhirter, Luella Frances (Smith). Addresses, 1896-1937; (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - McWhirter, Luella Frances (Smith): Diaries, 1884; 1927; (2 volumes) (Box 3)
  - McWhirter, Luella Frances (Smith): Diary sheets, 1894-1941 (Box 3)
  - Methodist Episcopal Church: Indiana State Council (Box 3)
  - Methodist Episcopal Church: Women's Foreign Missionary Society (Box 3)
  - Methodist Episcopal Church: Women's Home Missionary Society. Deaconess Home. Indiana conference (Box 3)
  - Minerva Club, Indianapolis (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous letters and papers:, 1873-1961; (7 folders) (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous letters and papers: Printed material (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous letters and papers: Newspaper clippings (Box 3)
  - Missions (Box 3)
  - National Congress of Parents and Teachers (Box 3)
  - National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs (Box 3)
  - National League of American Pen Women. Indiana branch (Box 3)
  - National Prohibition Emergency Committee (Box 3)
  - Near East relief (Box 3)
  - Peoples State Bank, Indianapolis (Box 3)
  - Perugia. Regia universita italiana per stranieri (Box 3)
  - Photographs. Obituaries and remembrances of Luella Frances (Smith) McWhirter, 1952 (Box 3)
  - President's Conference on Home Building and Home Ownership, Washington, D.C., 1930-1933; (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Prohibition (Box 3)
  - Scoggins, Ethel (McWhirter). (Box 3)
    Includes: Ethel McWhirter Scoggins: An Autobiography
  - Society of Indiana Pioneers (Box 3)
  - Southern Commercial Congress (Box 3)
  - United Protestant Church Loyalty Crusade (Box 3)
  - United States Good Roads Association, Inc. (Box 3)
  - U.S. Federal Housing Administration (Box 3)
  - Vellore, India. Missionary Medical College For Women (Box 3)
  - Women's Christian Temperance Union:, 1879-1950; (11 folders) (Box 4)
  - Women's Christian Temperance Union: Publicity department (Box 4)
  - Woman's Department Club, Indianapolis:, 1912-1954; (5 folders) (Box 4)
  - Woman's Department Club, Indianapolis: American Home Club Institute, 1926 (Box 4)
  - Woman's Department Club, Indianapolis: Newspaper clippings (Box 4)
  - Woman's Department Club, Indianapolis: Yearbooks, 1912-1915; 1937-1956; 1963-1965; 1968-1971; 1972-1975; 1976-1979; (32 volumes) (Box 4)
  - Woman's National Committee for Law Enforcement (Box 5)
  - Woman's Press Club of Indiana (Box 5)
  - Woman's Research Club, Indianapolis, Ind. (Box 5)
  - Women's Suffrage (Box 5)
  - Women's Union Christian Colleges in the Orient (Box 5)
  - YWCA (Box 5)
- II. Scrapbooks
  - Miscellaneous scrapbooks:, 1875-1939; 1895-1919; 1916-1929; 1921-1932; 1930-1939 (Box 5)
  - Armenian pageant, war victory, dry federation, etc., (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Badges, 1893-1938 (Box 5)
  - Better homes, 1926-1935 (Box 5)
  - Henry Long College for Women, Oriental colleges, Hoosier Program Bureau and legislative acts, etc., (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Indiana Federation of Clubs, 1909-1938; (3 folders) (Box 6)
  - Letterheads (Box 6)
  - Woman's Department Club: (early history), 1912-1924; 1922-1925; 1925-1926; 1926-1937 (Box 6)
  - Women's suffrage, 1913-1920 (Box 6)
  - W.T.C.U.:, 1888-1936; 1932-1933 (Box 6)
  - Undated bound scrapbook (Box 6)
- III. Printed
  - The Message (W.T.C.U.), 1916, Jan.- 1939, Dec.; (3 folders) (Box 6)
  - The Message (W.T.C.U.), 1940-1949; (3 folders) (Box 7)
  - Indiana Club Woman, 1927-1941; 1943-1947 (Box 7)
  - A 30-year History of the Indiana Federation of Clubs, 1938-1968 (Box 7)
  - Year Book of the Society of Indiana Pioneers, 1971 (Box 7)
  - History Indiana Federation of Clubs (Box 7)
  - Indianapolis Blue Book, 1925; 1929; (2 volumes) (Box 7)
  - Famous Living Americans (Box 7)
  - Women of Indiana (Box 7)
  - Women's Press Club of Indiana. Newspaper clipping, 1913 (Box 7)
  - The Indianapolis Sunday Star, part fiveVol. 35, No. 169., November 21, 1937 (Box Oversize)
    Features articles on the Indiana federation of clubs
  - The Message--Supplement. Reprint of letter by Mrs. McWhirtervol. III, no. 5., May 1899 (Box Oversize)
  - The Organizer, [Vol. I?, no. 1?], undated and Vol. I, no. 2Semi-monthly publication of the Woman's National Christian Temperance Union, November 1, 1882 (Box Oversize)
  - The Union Signal, Vol. XXIV, no. 10W.C.T.U. publication, March 10, 1898 (Box Oversize)
  - Miscellaneous clippings (Ovflat 33)
- IV. Photographs
  - Hezekiah Smith, Susan Smith, Smith family, 1840-1870; (5 photographs) (Box 7)
  - Luella Smith, 1864-1876; (7 photographs) (Box 7)
  - Felix McWhirter, 1875-1910; (2 photographs) (Box 7)
  - Luella Smith with others, 1870s.; (3 photographs) (Box 7)
  - Indiana Ashbury University, 1881 (Box 7)
  - Luella McWhirter Hutchins, 1888-1890; (2 photographs) (Box 7)
  - Luella Smith McWhirter, 1890; (2 photographs) (Box 7)
  - W.C.T.U. Assembly, Bay City, MI, 1895; (2 photographs) (Box 7)
  - W.C.T.U. Assemblies, WA and IN, 1896, 1900; (2 photographs) (Box 7)
  - Luella Smith McWhirter, 1897-1913; (7 photographs) (Box 7)
  - Luella Smith McWhirter, 1904-1912; (8 photographs) (Box 7)
  - Luella Smith McWhirter with other club members, ca. 1912; (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - W.C.T.U. and other banquets, 1916-1919; (5 photographs) (Box 7)
  - Peoples State Bank, Indianapolis, IN, 1918-1972; (12 photographs) (Box 7)
  - State School for the Deaf luncheon, 1920 (Box 7)
  - Luella Smith McWhirter and grandchildren, 1923 (Box 7)
  - Woman's Department Club, 1924, 1931; (3 photographs) (Box 7)
  - W.C.T.U. members. American Mission College for Girls, Cairo, Egypt, 1926; (8 photographs) (Box 7)
  - Mediterranean cruise, incl. Jerusalem, Algiers, Egypt, 1926-1927; (7 photographs) (Box 7)
  - W.C.T.U. Lausanne, Switzerland, 1928; (5 photographs) (Box 7)
  - Undated. Steven Marsters, (2 photographs) (Box 7)
  - Undated. W.C.T.U. leaders and members, (5 photographs) (Box 7)
  - Undated. Miscellaneous, (3 photographs) (Box 7)
  - McWhirter, Luella Smith, Glass transparency (Box 7)
  - Marsters, Rev. Stephen, Jr., Tintype (Box 7)
  - Smith, Rev. and Mrs. Hezekiah & Luella, Tintype (Box 7)
  - Smith, Captain Mark, Tintype (Box 7)
  - Smith, Peter, Tintype (Box 7)
  - National W.C.T.U. convention, dinner in Riley Room of Claypool Hotel, Indianapolis, 1918 (Ovflat 33)
  - Mrs. McWhirter at the State House, 1920 (Box Oversize)
  - Group photograph at State House, 1920 (Box Oversize)
  - Indiana Women at Chautauqua, New York, 1920 (Box Oversize)
  - Biannual conference of the General Federation of Women Clubs held at Armory, Grand Rapids, Michigan, May 31 to June 4, 1927 (Box Oversize)
  - Indiana convention W.C.T.U., Oct. 7-10 at Trinity M.E. Church, Elkhart, Indiana, ca. 1930 (Box Oversize)
  - Indiana Federation of Clubs, Riley Room, Claypool Hotel, Nov. 1-3, 1932 (Ovflat 33)
  - White House reception by President Hoover, General Federation of Women's Clubs, 1933, Jan. 11 (Box Oversize)
- V. Miscellaneous
  - Presentation trowel from Indiana Industrial School, April 8, 1898 (Box 7)
  - Pi Gamma Mu. Certificateenrollment card, undated, Mar. 15, 1929 (Box Oversize)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution. Certificate, Mar. 7, 1911 (Ovflat 33)
  - Broadside. To "Club Sisters" from Mrs. McWhirter, Indiana Federation of Clubs, War Victory Commission. Concerning furlough houses during WWI (Box Oversize)
  - Poster: "The Great Day!...at Bethany ParkFeatured speakers: Mrs. McWhirter, A.L. Crim (candidate for Secretary of State) and Professor J.E. Hawes (evangelist), Monday, July 22, 1906." (Box Oversize)
  - Poster: "An Up-To-Date 4th of July Picnic." Undated. Featured speakers: Mrs. McWhirter and Rev. E.G. Shouse of Kokomo (Box Oversize)